# Nazarii Pyndus

Front End Web Developer Email: <a href="mailto:npundus@gmail.com">npundus@gmail.com</a>

Skype: npundus

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nazarii-pyndus-97b278132

Personal Site: <a href="https://nazarii-pyndus.if.ua/">https://nazarii-pyndus.if.ua/</a>



## **Profile**

Front End Web Developer with near 4 years of commercial experience in software development mostly using Angular Framework. Familiarized with cross-browser and cross-device responsive web development. Result-orientated, responsible and attention to details. During this time I had the opportunities to work with several types of projects:

Healthcare - platform healthier working environment. Internet 3D market - creating Iframe external plugin with 3D Internet of Things - platform of manage light in building E-commerce - platform of booking

Creating mobile apps with Angular/Ionic and Flutter.

Also had experience as mentor, reviewer of code or lead of front-end team on the project, creating architecture of project and project structure from scratch.

## **Technical Skills**

Category	Skill list
Programming languages	JavaScript, TypeScript, Dart
Operating systems	Windows, Ubuntu, MacOS, Android, IOS
Libraries	Angular Material, AngularJS Material, ZingChart, Angular Bootstrap, UI-Cropper, Angular Paging, Angular Translate, RxJs, Lodash, Sweetalert, ngx-translate, Moment.JS, Moment-timezone, ng-color, ng-pick-datatime, ngx-mat-select-search, Chart.js, angular-calendar, datefns, bootstrap 4, JQuery, Google maps, Formspree, NGRX, NGXS, Formspree, Bootstrap, WebGL, Husky, ngx-spinner, ng-image-slider, prettier, ngx-infinite-scroll, an-qrcode
Technologies	Angular 2 +, AngularJS, Ionic 4+, Flutter
<b>Development tools</b>	Google DevTools, Avocode, Figma, Adobe Creative Cloud, WebStorm, VS Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Android Studio, Gulp, Xcode
RDBMS	SQL, POSTGRESQL
Web	HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JADE, PUG, FTL, Flutter Web

SCM	Git, GitLab, Github, Bitbucket
BTS	Redmine, Trello, Jira, Gitlab board

## **Education**

2017 - 2021

Ivano-Frankivsk National Technical University of Oil and Gas Bachelor's degree

Automation and computer-integration technologies, system engineer Ivano-Frankivsk, Ukraine

# Languages

• English — Intermediate

• Russian — Advanced

• Ukrainian — Native

# **Working experience**

October 2018 – present Ivano Frankivsk, Ukraine

Dates: 13 November 2018 - Present

**Role:** Front-End Developer

**About project:** Several web sites (service), with ability to configure and buy 2D/3D models of furniture. Plugin iframe in customer site.Platform that speeds up the whole process of furniture configuration and selling. It simplifies the process of ordering and selling furniture by using interactive 3D and AR technologies. Platform allows you to change colors in real time, materials, add or remove furniture elements and get the price instantly

**Description:** Change design and write or rewrite JavaScript/TypeScript, creating new projects, pages, architectures, writing custom: services, pipes, modal windows, Iframe plugins, mobile responsive, working with Unity (WebGL), bug fixing.

#### From October 2021 - present

Develop the external site in Angular 11, with ability to configure 3D furniture in your browser, also this site (microfrontend app) used in other sites as external feature of primary app. (Open part of the 3D app) used in customer site as extension.

**Development tools and Technologies:** Angular 8, Angular 11, AngularJS, Google DevTools, Avocode, Figma, WebStorm, WebGL

Dates: 5 May - 3 September 2021

Role: Angular Developer

**About project:** Admin site for trading app, that should help admins and managers to add a lot of new coins, creating trading description, sent the a lot of email template for different types of users **Description:** Designing and developing, mobile responsive, admin system developing of managing

trading platform

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 11, Google DevTools, Avocode

Dates: 28 January - 4 September 2021

Role: Angular Developer

About project: Service for viewing real estate for sale on the map and infrastructure in Dubai

Description: Designing and developing, mobile responsive, new Google Maps features, data

content creating (no backend), mail send

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 9, Google DevTools, Avocode, WebStorm,

Formspree

**Dates: 20 January 2021 – 1 September 2021** 

Role: Ionic Developer

About project: Application for Android and IOS to manage special brand meet drying or smoking

for creating the different types of dishes. Manage the temperature and humidity

Description: Creating builds, new design, new features

Development tools and Technologies: Android Studio, Mobile debug, Google DevTools,

WebStorm

Dates: 24 December 2020 - 9 February 2021

Role: Angular Developer

**About project:** Service helping companies to create a healthier working environment. The company takes unique assessments of the working culture and environment, as well as physical and psychosocial status of each employee. Based on this data, the service provides detailed company reports and ways for improvement.

**Description:** Write TypeScript, writing custom: services, pipes ,modal windows, responsive design

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 7, Google DevTools, Avocode, WebStorm

Dates: 5 January 2020 - 10 May 2020

Role: Front-End Developer

About project: The E-commerce project with ability to buy ticket for plain/bus/railway and book

the room/flat in Europe. And pay on the site without stuff

Description: Write TypeScript, redesign Pages, creating new modules, responsive design, bug

fixing

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 8, Google DevTools, Figma, WebStorm

**Dates: 5 January 2020 - May 2020** 

**Role:** Front-End Developer

**About project:** Main idea ability to manage light in all building with admin panel Write TypeScript, creating new projects, pages, architectures, writing custom: services, pipes ,modal windows, mobile responsive, creating Calendar events for Smart House, Color Picker RGB, custom for Warm Cold picker, bug fixing

**Description:** Write TypeScript, creating new projects, pages, architectures, writing custom: services, pipes, modal windows, mobile responsive, creating Calendar events for Smart House, Color Picker RGB, custom for Warm Cold picker, bug fixing

Development tools and Technologies: Angular 8, Google DevTools, Avocode, WebStorm